celebtella.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy policy | Celebtella

**(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

  * information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;
  * information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us;
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters;
  * any other information that you choose to send to us.

**(2) Cookies**

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We do not store any personal or identifiable information, however we may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer’s hard drive for up to 24 hours. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you. Our advertisers may also send you cookies.

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)

**(3) Using your personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

  * administer the website;
  * improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
  * enable your use of the services available on the website;
  * send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
  * send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications
  * provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

**(4) Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

**(5) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

**(6) Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
